The End of the Sea Did you know there's an
awesome treasure hidden
at the end of the sea?
And anyone who finds it,
the King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
Bon voyage, have the
courage to sail and believe.
And we will see a glimpse of
the sun rising on our tomorrow?
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons.
Sailed toward different dreams,
things have changed now.
For together we found, we looked
through the spyglass and see.
And we know that our hearts
have brought us here.
Where the conscious points our destiny.
There's no looking back,
take the hell with me!
Bon voyage, we can't stop all
our troubles, forget the past.
Though the future's
unclear, we still can smile.
We know we'll get there.
No regrets.
Every tear that we've cried only helps.
Our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Hey!
That's the wrong way, Zoro!
We're supposed to be going west!
You know, west, this way?
Jeez, I can't believe
your sense of direction.
But he's going east.
Oh, come on, Luffy.
Use your head for something
besides a hat rack for a change.
We're supposed to go to
the skull's right eye,
so we gotta go right, you rubber brain!
Why don't you go tell
those two heroes that we're
supposed to be heading south
before they end up lost?
Sure thing, Robin.
Luffy! Zoro! Wait up, guys!
South, huh?
You should have said so sooner.
Luffy, that's a pretty
neat stick you got there.
Isn't it?
It's mine, though.
You gotta get your own.
Isn't it?
It's mine, though.
You gotta get your own.
Aww, I want one.
Stick! Stick!
What's up with sticks?
You know,
I thought this course would be scarier,
but so far, it's been nice and peaceful.
Hey, Chopper, you're in
a pretty good mood today.
You feeling courageous for a change?
Yup, you betcha.
I feel so safe with these guys.
Yeah, you're right.
The forest really has
been a big disappointment.
Not to admit birds and trees for two whole
days makes me want to scream I'm so bored.
We haven't even seen
one of Eneru's priests,
so I know exactly how you
feel, Chopper. Do you?
Just listen to the two of you.
Are you that eager for
something dangerous to happen?
What in the hell?
Wind, good.
Helm, good.
This is so nice.
It's just like a pleasure cruise,
but we're making bad time.
Navigator, pick up the pace!
I'm afraid we can't, Captain Usopp.
The Milky Road gets
pretty steep in places,
so we have to rely on
dial power to get by.
Pour it on, little crow!
Sanji, you are my official bodyguard.
The captain is afraid
of this creepy forest.
Come on, for crying out loud.
The only person I'm planning on
protecting is my little Nami.
Hey, it's about time for that
weird knight's medicine, isn't it?
Do you remember where Chopper
said he was gonna put it?
Excuse me, dear.
My name is Gonfong.
That's Gonfong.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
I think he left it sitting on
a barrel down in the galley.
Can you grab it, Nami-sweet?
Old man.
Shall I tell you a little
of this land's history?
You back again, old man?
Get out now!
Enough, Wiper.
Gonefall is here to negotiate.
Negotiate what?
No, Chief. We're through.
We're not going to stand
by while two old men
negotiate away everything we
fought for our whole lives.
Listen, Gonfall.
You can forget about any kind of treaty.
If you want compromise so
badly, then give it all back.
For generations we've watched you sky
people slaughter us like little pigs.
Enough!
And now you're saying that
you want to make peace?
Ha!
I cannot give it all back to you.
The power of the Upper
Yard's birth is of the utmost
importance to every man and
woman now living in Scypia.
All are grateful for its many blessings.
I have no right to take that away.
These people are, after all, innocent.
Oh, so the Scypia people
are innocent, are they?
I guess you can call them
that since they let you do
their fighting for them and
never bloody their own hands.
Maybe it's time we involved
a few innocent people.
I won't allow that.
You want peace so badly.
Make a sacrifice.
Execute a hundred of
your own innocent people
on the ancient altar and
bring us their heads.
You're mad.
I won't.
Then we're done talking.
Get lost, or I'll take your
head as a down payment.
Wait, wiper.
Be careful when you use my name, old man.
I am quite fond of the juice
made from your pumpkins.
I'll kill you!
Wiper, stop!
Warriors, restrain him!
What is this? Kamakiri!
Braum, not you two!
Aisa cries a lot, doesn't she, Nurse?
Yes, she always cries when there's
a disturbance in the village.
It's Wiper, right?
I really don't know but
you have to admit when
there are problems in
the village he's right
in the middle of them
why what do you think of
him Lock I think that
he frightens me as well
he's like a demon
The...
The Fourth!
Wiper!
I told you before!
That's Isha's treasure!
You have no right to...
But Brahm...
We can't assume we'll get
another chance like this.
I won't let this opportunity pass.
If you don't think you're
up to it, stay behind.
I won't hold it against you.
Don't say that.
You know we're up to it. Are you?
Are you up to abandoning anyone
who falls during the battle?
If you can step over the bodies of
your dying comrades and keep fighting,
then follow me.
Now, I swear, Enoru's head is mine.
Until six years ago, I was gone.
Uh, did you hit your head, old man?
As you have no doubt learned,
it is believed that the Upper Yard first
appeared in Skypiea abruptly
a good 400 years ago.
Until then, Skypiea had always
been a peaceful Sky Island.
Items from the Blue Sea that were
occasionally brought here by the
knock-up stream were rare and
valuable treasures to the Sky people.
Likewise,
all of the Fourth on the Sky Islands
was brought here by the knock-up stream.
But a quantity of Fourth
as vast as the upper yard
appearing in the sky seemed
like an unimaginable miracle.
The Sky People were understandably
overjoyed and worshipped it as holy ground,
a gift from heaven itself.
But the original inhabitants
were still on that birth,
and a war erupted over its possession.
Those inhabitants were the Shandians.
Then they're the gorillas?
So,
you're saying the Shandians used to live
on Jaya when it was still in the Blue Sea?
That's right.
The current blasted them into
the sky against their will.
Hold on, does that mean that you just
stole the land that was rightfully theirs?
It does.
The Sky People's greed drove them
to steal the Shandorians' homeland.
And for the last 400 years,
the war between the Shandians and the
Sky People has gone on without a break.
The Shandians are simply trying
to regain their lost home.
How sad.
All those lives lost. Wait a second!
Doesn't that make you the bad guy?
I'm sorry.
But I'm afraid that's correct.
Oh, my medicine.
Excuse me, I almost forgot to take it.
What about Eneru?
Who's he?
What's his story?
While I was still gone,
he appeared from another Sky
Island, leading a group of warriors.
They dealt a heavy blow to my
Divine Squad and to the Shandians.
Then they seized control
of the Upper Yarn.
That was six years ago.
Since then nearly all the
Divine Squad have been
enslaved and forced to
perform some mysterious labor.
I don't know what it is.
But the Shandians don't care who God is.
They want what they've always
wanted, the return of their homeland.
Yeah, right.
If all these Shandians are interested
in is getting their homeland back,
then why did they attack
us the minute we showed up?
The members of the Divine
Squad sometimes steal a
ship in hopes that they might
escape from Enderu. However,
the Shandians still consider
the Divine Squad enemies,
and they will eliminate them on sight.
They must have mistaken you for them.
Oh, of course.
That makes it all better.
One reason I became the Sky
Knight was to help these
escapees make it safely
away to other Sky Islands.
There is no place on
the Upper Yard that such
outlaws would be able
to avoid Eneru's eye.
To hear the way you tell it,
this Eneru guy sounds like
he must be the devil himself.
For all we know,
he's out there right now listening to
every word we're saying and taking notes,
notes, notes!
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
Hey, don't tell me you've
suddenly become a convert.
Hey, you heard what the
old man said. Scary.
The devil himself?
No, but he comes very close.
Eneru has decreed that all outsiders
like yourselves are criminals.
What's more,
he has made the inhabitants of Skypiea
responsible for leading them to judgment.
This gives rise to the
islander's sense of guilt.
When the people believe they
are committing a criminal act,
they become overwhelmed by it.
It weakens their will.
Eneru knows this and exploits it.
He has created a flock of
helpless lambs to rule over.
The lives of the people
are like playthings to him.
The devil indeed.
When we landed on Angel Beach we thought
we'd found something like a paradise.
Boy were we wrong!
Of all the places that
ancient city of gold
could have ended up being
this is just our luck.
Oh!
That's right this city
you sure were excited
about it but please tell
me something what is gold?
Run for it!
It's a giant snake!
It's enormous.
I wonder if it's another
result of the environment here.
Okay, Catfish Face, it's
time for you to get belayed.
How in the hell can something
so big move so freaking fast?
Uh, change of plan. We're running away.
Sounds good.
Don't let that venom
touch you! It's death!
Oh!
Hey, Mr. Snake! Over here! Follow me!
Better hurry up!
Your dinner's getting away!
Robin!
Look out!
He goes here!
Ha! Nice try!
That was awesome, Robin!
Good.
I finally managed to make my
way around the back of it.
Crap!
This way, whispers! Over here!
This is her.
I know I'm on the right path,
but when are you missing from me?
Are they lost?
Should I pay for that?
I'm lost, guys! Wait for me!
Well, it figures.
I turn my back for one second
and they go and get lost on me.
Oh, whatever.
They know how to take care of themselves.
And I got most of the
map memorized anyway.
I go to the right.
Now what?
Where did everybody go?
Did they get lost?
I better keep moving.
I'll catch up with them
later at the ruins.
Robin said we had to go south, and it
always gets warmer when you go south?
so I go this way.
When we first met, I acted as a
soldier for hire to protect you.
Because you blue sea
dwellers are unfamiliar
with the ways of sky warfare
sky warfare. What do you mean?
Now observe with someone explained
to me why we're doing this
all will be clear now strike that
shell with all of your might!
Young man take it easy Sanji
if you put a hole in my deck?
I'll put enough holes in you
to make a Swiss cheese jealous!
hit it with all the strength you've got!
Respect for other people's property
when you're a guest old man.
Well, it's your show, old-timer.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Do you have to wind up into it like that?
Whoa.
That was just sad.
I know I said take it easy, but you
didn't have to be that pathetic.
You didn't even put a ding in the barrel.
No.
I gave that swing everything I had.
Like I was really trying
to put a hole in the deck.
Hey, now.
It sounds crazy, but it's like this shell
absorbed all the force of the impact.
Now,
if you'd be so good as
to turn the shell's holes
towards the barrel and lightly
press the tip on the back.
You're familiar with the
operation of dial power, yes?
Right here?
That my friends is an
impact dial it absorbs any
impact it receives and
then releases the energy.
When it's pressed it is
frequently affixed to
the palm of the hand with
a glove or a bandage.
A direct hit from one
of these has more than
enough power to kill an
average person easily.
I know. Usopp?
Yeah, you're right.
That's what that butterball
priest was using.
I warned you, didn't I?
Impact!
Why didn't you warn us?
That scared the hell out of me, old man!
I have heard that in ancient
times on other Sky Islands,
there existed dials even
more powerful than this one.
The so-called Reject Dial was said
to be capable of magnifying the
energy it stored and released ten
times the power of a mere impact dial.
But that incredible power
was a double-edged sword,
for it threatened the life of the
attacker as well as his opponent.
As a result, it was very rarely used.
These little shells are that dangerous
they're worse than any weapon I know.
Yeah I thought Dials were supposed
to be common everyday objects so they
are but it seems that man has a talent
for Finding deadly uses for beneficial
discoveries no matter how mundane
they may seem to be it all Depends
upon the user dials are very useful
when applied in battle their Powerful
destruction can be awesome for
example the heat dial used for cooking
Can be placed inside a lance and used
to generate thermal energy creating
the Deadly weapon known as the heat
javelin or the flame dial which stores
fire can Be placed in the mouth of a
bird creating a creature that seems
to breathe fire yeah Chopper mentioned
something like that and that's sky
warfare it is blue sea dwellers who
know Nothing of dials have no way of
seeing through these tricks the same
holds true for our many Types of
artificial clouds the priests have
forged these into forms they can control
if you Don't understand them you'll
be helpless against them wait a sec
then is there any truth to that Mantra
thing that tubby was talking about
that let him predict our moves yes
mantra unfortunately I'm afraid that
i myself am unable to use it so it's
rather difficult for me to explain
Mantra is described as an ability
to hear the ideas that as long
as a person lives his or her
Body emits its own voice a voice
yes by listening to the voice
you're supposed to be able to know
Your opponent's next move with
practice and training you can hear
these voices over a very Large
area the priests can hear over all
of the upper yard enaru's powers
extend across this Entire land
the exact nature of those powers
remains a mystery but because of
them the people People of this land
can never know a moment's ease.
I wonder if they've made
it down yet. Yes, Lord.
They are lying in wait as we speak.
The three priests have
placed their ordeals,
and Commander Yama has taken
fifty divine warriors with him.
My Lord, it looks as though
this is becoming an Alto war.
Is it really necessary
to go to such extremes?
The Shandians and a few blue sea
dwellers hardly seem worth it.
Come now.
The more players there
are, the more fun the game.
You, my hairy friend, underestimate
the power of sky warfare.
Sky warfare, my lord? That's right.
You'll see soon enough.
Heal that for me, would you?
Now let's see.
We have the fifty divine warriors at our
disposal, plus our three surly priests.
Including me?
That's fifty-four.
There are twenty Shandians
heading toward the island,
the four blue sea-dwellers in the forest,
and the four escaping down the Milky Road.
No, wait, that's only three.
The old man can't fight anymore.
Altogether, that makes eighty-one.
This battle will determine
who will be left standing.
Shall we guess how many will
remain after three hours' time?
Pardon, Lord.
You wish us to make a game out of death?
Oh, why don't you lighten up?
You, take a guess. What?
Are you talking to me, my Lord?
But I...
I don't know anything about it.
I'm just a humble servant girl.
Oh, come on.
What's wrong with you people?
You're no fun.
Just take a guess.
Any guess at all.
All right, then.
You try it.
Go ahead.
Guess.
Well um the three priests are all
very strong of course and those divine
warriors are all extremely powerful
as well i doubt many of them will
be defeated but the enemy has shown
their power rivals the priests so
in three hours time i think 30 will
fall leaving let's see 81 minus 30?
Leaving 51 alive, how's that?
51, eh?
That's your best guess?
Don't you think you're being just a little
optimistic, or are you just squeamish?
I think you're underestimating
the results of this battle.
Uh, then what do you think,
my lord, if I may ask?
Well, it's obvious if only
you'd give it a little thought.
In three hours, of the 81 fighters now on
this island, all that will be left are...
Five.
What the?
I can't move.
What's happening?
Why'd I stop moving?
Greetings, my Shandora friends.
You're looking well.
I'm glad you could come to my party.
Shut up! Now, now.
I appreciate your enthusiasm,
but honestly, I know my own name.
I'm afraid I've got some very bad news.
There have been a few changes made
here on Upper Yard since last night.
Can't move, can you?
Too bad.
You only have a 3 % chance of surviving.
The Ordeal of String.
No, not the Ordeal of String!
I would have warned you, but then I
thought, why ruin the surprise for them?
It's string cloud.
Oh, very good.
I'm impressed.
It's spread throughout my area too.
Thin to be seen.
But so tough that even the
strongest man can't break free.
Once entangled.
My mighty string clown.
You fools have been
wrapping yourselves up in
it from the moment you
set foot in this forest.
Take a look around.
Your bodies are covered in string.
You've all become my puppets.
Mere playthings at my disposal.
Yes.
All of you except for one.
Fly, Vice!
WIPER!
You can't beat me in the air, you fool!
Look out!
That's a heat javelin!
Why did you throw away
your shield and weapon?
Are you insane?
No, you wouldn't dare!
Take it.
If all you want's a shoulder, it's yours.
An impact dial?
But that can't kill me.
No.
Ten times that power.
Reject dial!
And the upper yard survival game has
its first casualty now only 80 remain so.
The first battle has
ended in a stunning upset!
Shit is finished.
What? But how?
Like you, Shit underestimated
the power of sky warfare.
The fool.
But surely this is a disaster.
No priest has been defeated in six years,
and now suddenly two have fallen
in as many days. Nonsense.
So they were defeated.
So what?
Perhaps they lacked divine protection.
Listen up, men.
We're up against 20 Xandorians
and seven blue sea-dwellers.
They pose no threat.
We don't need to trouble
the priests with them.
Destroy them without mercy. Go.
If you can step over the bodies of
your dying comrades and keep fighting?
then follow me.
Now, I swear, Inneru's head will be mine.
Once we kill Inneru,
there will be no need for you to sneak
around obsessing over a single bag of Fourth.
A single bag of Fourth.
Wiper, what were you thinking?
Just try using that reject dial again!
You'll blow your body to pieces.
It's my body, isn't it?
I warned you—we'd have to take
risks if we wanted victory.
We'll never beat them if we
aren't willing to make sacrifices!
Understand?
understand
Damn fool.
What are you all standing
around for? What's that?
We're in the middle of enemy
territory, so let's split up.
There are still two priests
out there left to deal with.
It looks like they've changed
the location of their ordeals.
We can't have everyone getting
caught in the same ordeal again.
We have to be smarter than that.
I'm going ahead.
Huh. Fine, then.
Do whatever you want.
Just don't forget to pray for our safety.
Okay, men.
Let's be careful.
We'll meet at God's Shrine.
Hey, you!
Are you mad?
House?
A divine soldier? Correct.
By order of Almighty Eneru,
we've been commanded to purge his enemies
from the width and breadth of Upper Yard.
We are Lord Eneru's Elite.
There is no place for you to hide.
We possess the power of the Axtile,
which is not found in Skypiea.
Out of my way!
Your efforts are futile.
Your shot's useless.
Axtile!
Your shield won't help you!
Oh, the islands in the south are warm.
And their heads get really hot.
They grow up pineapples,
they grow up coconuts.
And they're morons?
A goat?
Was that a goat?
Where is it?
Here go!
Who's this jerk?
Man, he got me all excited.
I thought I was gonna get to see a goat.
Next verse.
Islands in the north are snowy.
And their heads get really cold!
They're very chilly-chilly, they're
very willy-nilly, and they're idiots!
Oh, it's you.
That's right.
And just what are you doing here?
I warned you to leave
this island. Shut up!
I can do whatever I want!
No, you can't.
This island belongs to us
Shandians. Huh? Really? It does?
I thought it was God's.
Well then, I beg your pardon.
Next verse!
Islands in the east of
- Hold it! Oh, what?
No.
I'm through wasting words on you.
And I'm sick and tired of
listening to your idiotic babbling.
So I'm gonna destroy you.
I see.
If you want to fight,
you just have to say so.